AYDEN LEE

Backend Developer

\$\ 13968114566 @ coiiasd88@gmail.com \@ https://github.com/coffiasd

SUMMARY

I'm 32 years old. I have been working as a backend developer for over 10 years.In the first 5 years, I worked with **PHP**.I did some website development with PHP. In the following 3 years I did some **GOLANG** development for a game company.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts in Computer Science B. A.

2007 - 2011

Ningbo University of Technology

LANGUAGES

chinese Native •••• english Advanced ••••

PROJECTS

Epic-nfts 2022

china

a NFT project build with solidity

- a website to call our blockchain API
- mint NFT

Gateway 2021

china

RPCX Gateway

- handle http request to our back-end micro-service
- control the request rate of our back-end micro-service
- register a micro-service by etcd

Article-Center-Microservice

2020

china

Article Management Platform

- provide a platform to manage our company articles
- provide a RPC API to company project
- other projects can get an article by rpc request with some parameters

Operation-Center-Microservice

2019 - 2021

china

Game operation platform

- · record game user events by RPC request
- provide a website to show daily user information
- provide some data to help our Operators trace user
- provide a website to help our Operators manage game



SKILLS

php · golang · solidity · vue · react

FIND ME ONLINE

▼ Twitter

www.twitter.com/coffiasse

git GitHub

www.github.com/coffiasd

EXPERIENCE

Web3

Freelance

2021 - 2022 China. Hangzhou

Freelance

• Smart Contract Developer

GOLANG Developer

浙江无端科技

2016 - 2021 China. Hangzhou

Game company

- Back-end Developer
- Front-end Developer

PHP Developer

杭州落北科技

2012 - 2016 china. Hangzhou

E-commerce, company

- PHP
- CSS/HTML/JQUERY

PROJECTS

Company-Official-Website

2018 - 2018

china

Official Website

- show some recently news of our company
- provide a forum for our users to discussing our games
 provide a customer service page for our users to contacting us
 provide a latest download link about our game